Hello. Today we are going to talk about redemption. 
First, redemption means that humanity can be saved from sin
Through the cross of Jesus. 

There is the word of redemption In Romans 3:24.
All are justified freely by his grace through the redemption 
That came by Christ Jesus.

So today we will talk about these topics, 
First we will see about the sequences of Lord’s Kingdom and salvation,
And about the reality of the kingdom.
And also we will talk about the eschatological(에스커털 라지컬) tension, and Holy Spirit, 
And the life of a saved Christian

—————————————————

As a result, we were saved by Jesus' cross and excused(익스큐즈드) of all sins. We became a citizen of heaven and experience the history of the Holy Spirit in our life.

So, as a Christian, we should look at the eternal heaven, waiting for the day when Jesus will come again. And we should not forget the love of God who saved us, and also, we should live preparing for the kingdom of God that will come again.

Thank you for listening!
